<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Arrow News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Cubs vs. Padres prediction and odds for Saturday, June 3 (San Diego will get to Smyly)</title>
		<link>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/cubs-vs-padres-prediction-and-odds-for-saturday-june-3-san-diego-will-get-to-smyly/</link>
					<comments>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/cubs-vs-padres-prediction-and-odds-for-saturday-june-3-san-diego-will-get-to-smyly/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sportshub]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/?p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Chicago Cubs and San Diego Padres will face-off for the second time in as many days on Saturday night. The Cubs squeaked by the Padres in the opening game of the series, winning by a final score of 2-1. They’ll roll with Drew Smyly (3.45 ERA) in Game 2. He’ll face-off against Yu Darvish [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="speakable-content">The Chicago Cubs and San Diego Padres will face-off for the second time in as many days on Saturday night.</p>
<p class="speakable-content">The Cubs squeaked by the Padres in the opening game of the series, winning by a final score of 2-1. They’ll roll with Drew Smyly (3.45 ERA) in Game 2. He’ll face-off against Yu Darvish (4.61 ERA) of the Padres.</p>
<p>Let’s take a look at the odds for the game and then I’ll give you my best bet.</p>
<h3 class="speakable-content">Cubs vs. Padres odds, run line, and total</h3>
<h3>Cubs vs. Padres prediction and pick</h3>
<p>Drew Smyly could be in for a rough night tonight as he has to take on a Padres team that’s significantly better against left-handed pitchers. The Padres OPS increases from .672 against right-handed pitchers to .740 against lefties.</p>
<p>Smyly has faced the Padres once already this season, giving up four hits and two earned runs in only 5.0 innings in a game that the Cubs ended up losing by a final score of 5-3.</p>
<p>The Cubs offense has gone ice cold lately, ranking 29th in OPS over the past 14 days.</p>
<p>There’s no reason why the Padres can’t pounce on this Chicago club and get the win as home favorites.</p>
<p><em><strong>Game odds refresh periodically and are subject to change.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/cubs-vs-padres-prediction-and-odds-for-saturday-june-3-san-diego-will-get-to-smyly/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Steelers first-round pick already proving his teammates wrong</title>
		<link>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/steelers-first-round-pick-already-proving-his-teammates-wrong/</link>
					<comments>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/steelers-first-round-pick-already-proving-his-teammates-wrong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sportshub]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pittsburgh Steelers rookie Broderick Jones is already proving teammates wrong.  The Pittsburgh Steelers selected DT Broderick Jones from Georgia with the 14th pick in April’s NFL Draft. Most objective viewers would watch that happen and think well, yeah, duh — of course Broderick Jones will start at left tackle for the young, rebuilding Steelers next season. Not Steelers left [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="speakable-content"><em><strong>Pittsburgh Steelers rookie Broderick Jones is already proving teammates wrong. </strong></em></p>
<p class="speakable-content">The Pittsburgh Steelers selected DT Broderick Jones from Georgia with the 14th pick in April’s NFL Draft. Most objective viewers would watch that happen and think well, yeah, duh — <em>of course</em> Broderick Jones will start at left tackle for the young, rebuilding Steelers next season.</p>
<p>Not Steelers left guard Kevin Dotson, who appeared on the Three Point Stance Podcast and gave a very honest, if misguided opinion on Jones’ upcoming rookie season. He instead vouched for veteran lineman Dan Moore Jr., who has 34 starts in two seasons with Pittsburgh.</p>
<p>Jones, however, is already exceeding the expectations of at least one teammate, it would seem.</p>
<h2 class="speakable-content">Broderick Jones getting first team reps at left tackle for Pittsburgh Steelers</h2>
<p>To almost nobody’s surprise, Jones is getting first-team reps at left tackle for the Steelers.</p>
<p>Fresh off two straight national titles at UGA, Jones was one of the most highly regarded prospects at his position in years. He will now be tasked with protecting Kenny Pickett in the pocket as Pittsburgh embraces a new era following Ben Roethlisberger’s retirement.</p>
<p>Dan Moore, meanwhile, is taking reps at right tackle. A notable change in position, but not the demotion one might’ve feared when Jones’ name was called on draft night.</p>
<p>As for Kevin Dotson… he is actually facing a demotion. Free agent Isaac Seumalo is expected to take snaps from Dotson at left guard. A cruel twist of the ironic knife.</p>
<p>Of course, Dotson was never actually criticizing Jones or making grand proclamations. Offhanded comments on podcasts can easily be taken out of context and it’s better to view his sentiments as confidence in Moore, not as being explicitly jealous of Jones.</p>
<p>But, by that same token, it can be hard for veteran players to accept an influx of young talent, especially when teams like Pittsburgh are prioritizing player development over winning games. Dotson started all 17 games for Pittsburgh last season. Now, if healthy, one has to expect Jones will start all 17 games for the Steelers in 2023.</p>
<p>To rub salt in the wound, Seumalo — on the verge of replacing Dotson — spoke very glowingly of his new teammate Broderick Jones. From Steeler Nation:</p>
<p>The Steelers should expect big things from Jones. He succeeded at the highest level of college football. Now, he’s ready to tackle the pros.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/steelers-first-round-pick-already-proving-his-teammates-wrong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Re-grading every NBA Draft night trade from 2022</title>
		<link>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/re-grading-every-nba-draft-night-trade-from-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/re-grading-every-nba-draft-night-trade-from-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sportshub]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The 2022 NBA Draft featured several influential trades. With the benefit of hindsight, let’s grade each move that was made.  The 2022 NBA Draft introduced several future stars into the league. Paolo Banchero, the No. 1 pick, is already the centerpiece of the Orlando Magic rebuild. Chet Holmgren is about to accentuate and elevate a burgeoning contender [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="speakable-content"><em>The 2022 NBA Draft featured several influential trades. With the benefit of hindsight, let’s grade each move that was made. </em></p>
<p class="speakable-content">The 2022 <a href="https://fansided.com/nba/nba-draft/">NBA Draft</a> introduced several future stars into the league. Paolo Banchero, the No. 1 pick, is already the centerpiece of the Orlando Magic rebuild. Chet Holmgren is about to accentuate and elevate a burgeoning contender in OKC. Then there’s Jalen Williams, Jaden Ivey, Jabari Smith, Keegan Murray — all players who feel destined for long, successful NBA careers.</p>
<p>Of course, the NBA Draft is shaped not only by the picks made — but by who makes them, and how. Trades are commonplace on draft night. More often than not, they’re rampant. The 2023 NBA Draft will be no different, with speculation already bubbling up around Portland with the No. 3 pick and Houston with the No. 4 pick.</p>
<p>While the 2022 NBA Draft didn’t feature any high-profile trade swings of that magnitude, there were several noteworthy players moved around. Rebuilds were reshaped, contenders shed salary, and cash considerations made their famous annual appearance on the NBA red carpet.</p>
<p>Let’s go through all the significant NBA Draft night trades and re-grade them with the benefit of hindsight.</p>
<h2 class="speakable-content">NBA Draft trade grade: Warriors-Hawks swap 2nds</h2>
<p>Both Tyrese Martin and Ryan Rollins appeared in fewer than 20 games for their respective teams and shot below 40 percent from the field. Both being second-round picks on contenders, neither was expected to contribute much — and neither gained much traction during the regular season. This feels like a wash.</p>
<p><strong>Warriors</strong>: C</p>
<p><strong>Hawks</strong>: C</p>
<h2>NBA Draft trade grade: Grizzlies trade for Kennedy Chandler</h2>
<p>A few months ago, this trade grade would have heavily favored the Grizzlies, who received Tennessee’s Kennedy Chandler — a first-round caliber of prospect — in exchange for cash and a future pick that may or may not be anything.</p>
<p>Well, the Grizzlies cut Chandler in April to make room for undrafted free agent and G-League star Kenneth Lofton. So the Spurs are the winners here by default, whether that future pick becomes anything or not.</p>
<p><strong>Spurs</strong>: A</p>
<p><strong>Grizzlies</strong>: F</p>
<h2>NBA Draft trade grade: Mavericks trade for Jaden Hardy</h2>
<p>Jaden Hardy emerged as a real asset for Dallas late in the season. With their depth depleted after the Kyrie Irving trade, the Mavs leaned on Hardy’s shot-making talent in the second unit. The former G-League Ignite guard answered the call and looked like one of the more promising rookies from outside the lottery.</p>
<p>We can never really know the outcome until the Kings use those future picks, but Dallas spent practically nothing for a legitimate rotation player. Hard not to chalk that up as a win.</p>
<p><strong>Kings</strong>: D</p>
<p><strong>Mavericks</strong>: A</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/re-grading-every-nba-draft-night-trade-from-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ump show: White Sox walk it off as home plate umpire takes a spill</title>
		<link>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/ump-show-white-sox-walk-it-off-as-home-plate-umpire-takes-a-spill/</link>
					<comments>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/ump-show-white-sox-walk-it-off-as-home-plate-umpire-takes-a-spill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sportshub]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The White Sox walked off against the Tigers on an unusual play as the home plate empire took a wild pitch to the face and runners advanced. We’ve all seen walk-offs before but Saturday’s action between the White Sox and Tigers brought a new and unique addition to the collection. Chicago had the bases loaded [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The White Sox walked off against the Tigers on an unusual play as the home plate empire took a wild pitch to the face and runners advanced.</p>
<p>We’ve all seen walk-offs before but Saturday’s action between the White Sox and Tigers brought a new and unique addition to the collection.</p>
<p>Chicago had the bases loaded in the bottom of the 10th in a 1-1 tie against the Tigers. With two outs, Detroit’s Jose Cisnero just needed to retire the next batter to keep the game alive.</p>
<p>Cisnero ended the game in favor of the White Sox with his first pitch of the at-bat and sent home plate umpire Cory Blaser to the dirt.</p>
<p>Incredibly, all three runs in the game were scored on wild pitches.</p>
<p>Ump show: White Sox walk it off as home plate umpire takes a spill</p>
<p>Cisnero sent a wild pitch right at the facemask of the umpire, knocking him to the ground. The ball bounded away as Yoan Moncada sprinted for home to score the winning run.</p>
<p>Tigers catcher Eric Haase figured out pretty quickly that Detroit wasn’t going to be able to make the play. He and White Sox batter Tim Anderson went to check on Blaser, who stayed down as the run scored.</p>
<p>The reaction of the crowd summed it up really. It was a shocking way to walk off a game.</p>
<p>The White Sox and Tigers needed extra innings to decide things in part because neither sides pitching staff could keep things under control. Andrew Benintendi scored on a wild pitch from Michael Lorenzen in the fourth inning. In the sixth, Detroit returned the favor when Zach McKinstry scored on Dylan Cease’s second wild pitch of the outing.</p>
<p>Regardless of how it transpired, the White Sox got their second straight win over the Tigers. They’ll meet again on Sunday afternoon to finish the series.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://slot-5000.sinonjs.org/2023/06/04/ump-show-white-sox-walk-it-off-as-home-plate-umpire-takes-a-spill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
